<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EffL @ POSTECH</title>
    <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EffL @ POSTECH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Focus</title>
      <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/focus/</guid>
      <description>The long-term goal of EffL is to make AI more responsible&amp;ndash;accessible, sustainable, and righteous.
As the first step, we are focusing on various facets of Efficient ML, which could help us make AI equally accessible to anybody on Earth, with no extreme carbon emission.
In particular, we work on three dimensions:
Inference. We develop fast, low-resource methods to serve massive multimodal AI, e.g., Model Compression Parallel Decoding Batch Scheduling Training. We resolve the compute / memory bottlenecks for training large-scale models, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/papers/</guid>
      <description>We mainly target top-tier ML conferences, e.g., NeurIPS / ICML / ICLR.
Sometimes, we also submit to domain-specific venues that involve ML, e.g., Vision/Language/Speech.
2024 # The Role of Masking for Efficient Supervised Knowledge Distillation of Vision Transformers
Seungwoo Son, Jegwang Ryu, Namhoon Lee, and Jaeho Lee
ECCV 2024 (ICLR 2023 workshop: Sparsity in Neural Networks, IPIU 2023 Oral 🥉)
Neural Image Compression with Text-guided Encoding for both Pixel-level and Perceptual Fidelity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/collaborators/</guid>
      <description>Our recent industry collaborators include:
Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology: ICML 2024, TMLR 2023 Google: As a visiting faculty researcher, and as a student intern DeepMind: ICML 2023 NAVER: NAACL 2024 Krafton: CVPR 2024 VPIX medical: (Private project) In addition, we have worked with universities abroad:
University College London: NeurIPS 2023, ICML 2023 University of Michigan: CVPR 2024 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
