<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EffL @ POSTECH</title>
    <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EffL @ POSTECH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Focus</title>
      <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/focus/</guid>
      <description>Our long-term goal is to make AI more responsible&amp;ndash;accessible, sustainable, and righteous.
As the first step, we focus on various facets of Efficient ML, which helps us make AI equally accessible to everyone.
In particular, we work on three dimensions:
Inference. We develop fast, low-resource methods to serve massive multimodal AI, e.g., Model Compression Parallel Decoding Batch Scheduling Training. We resolve the compute / memory bottlenecks for training large-scale models, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/papers/</guid>
      <description>We mainly target top-tier ML conferences, and other domain-specific venues that involve ML.
2025 # Towards Federated Low-Rank Adaptation with Rank-Heterogeneous Communication
Yuji Byun and Jaeho Lee
NAACL 2025 (NeurIPS 2024 AFM Workshop)
Fast Training of Sinusoidal Neural Fields via Scaling Initialization
Taesun Yeom,* Sangyoon Lee,* and Jaeho Lee
ICLR 2025
ZIP: An Efficient Zeroth-order Prompt Tuning for Black-box Vision-Language Models
Seonghwan Park, Jaehyeon Jeong, Yongjun Kim, Jaeho Lee, and Namhoon Lee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effl.postech.ac.kr/docs/research/collaborators/</guid>
      <description>Our recent industry collaborators include:
Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology: ICML 2024, TMLR 2023 Google: EMNLP 2024; as a visiting faculty researcher, and as a student intern DeepMind: ICML 2023 NAVER: NAACL 2024 Krafton: CVPR 2024 VPIX medical: (Private project) In addition, we have worked with universities abroad:
University College London: NeurIPS 2023, ICML 2023 University of Michigan: CVPR 2024 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
